It unraveled quickly when I couldn't answer
the question "How did you two meet?"
- l would've thought at a horse show.
- Oh, that's good.
(Amy:)Mm.
l panicked and said Woodstock.
l just wanted to show Sheldon off
to my family.
(Penny:)Sure, I get that. I mean,
he's your first boyfriend and all.
(Amy:)Not just my first boyfriend. He's the best
boyfriend. I mean, think about it.
(Amy:)I'm dating Sheldon Cooper.
(Penny:)Yes, on purpose.
(Amy:)He's handsome, he's lanky, he's brilliant.
(Amy:)His skin has that pale, waxy quality.
(Penny:)Well, sickly is the new sexy.
(Howard:)- Yeah.
- Mm.
(Penny:)You know, Amy...
(Penny:)...when you're in a relationship
with someone you really care about...
(Penny:)...the sucky part is
it leaves you open to getting hurt.
(Amy:)Do you ever worry about Leonard
doing that to you?
Ha, ha, that's hilarious. No.